# WynNelson

Analytic web developer whose focus is on the prototyping, testing, and implementation stages of UX design. Trained to effectively communicate complex institutional knowledge to both experts and nonexperts. Strong self-starter who consistently seeks additional professional development.

P: 774-633-0845

E: wynlnelson@gmail.com

W: wynnelson.com

in: linkedin.com/in/wynnelson

: github.com/wynnelson

# **Education**

## North Carolina State University

### **Master of Science in Mathematics**

Demonstrated expertise in pure mathematics and researched solution counting of multivariate polynomial Pham systems

# Gordon College

## **Bachelor of Science in Mathematics, Minor in Computer Science**

Graduated summa cum laude and with departmental honors

# Experience

Aug 2016 - Current North Carolina State University

## **Teaching Graduate Student**

NC State University is a leading public land-grant research university and is the largest university in the Carolinas. I effectively communicated technical concepts to over 175 students while instructing four undergraduate mathematics courses. I also adaptively developed all course materials for an asynchronous online course.

Jun 2016 – Aug 2016 Jun 2015 – Aug 2015

# Cell Signaling Technology

#### Research Assistant

CST is a biotech company that produces antibodies and other reagents related to the study of cell signaling pathways. I created visualization tools to study DNA sequencing clusters as networks and to efficiently identify true from false sequence origins.

# Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

UX Design

UI Design

Sketch

Unix

Python

Wireframing

Analytic Thinking

Data Analysis

# Certifications

Introduction to Design
Teaching and Communication
Inclusive Teaching
Accessibility in the Classroom
Project SAFE Ally

Springboard

NC State Graduate School

NC State Office of Faculty Development

NC State IT Accesibility Office

NC State Office for Institutional Equity and Diversity